{"test_questions": [[{"question": "A TRIAC:", "opta": "can trigger only on positive gate voltages", "optb": "can trigger only on negative gate voltages", "optc": "cannot be triggered with gate voltages", "optd": "can be triggered by either a positive or a negative gate voltage", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When checking a good SCR or TRIAC with an ohmmeter it will:", "opta": "show high resistance in both directions", "optb": "show low resistance with positive on anode and negative on cathode, and high resistance when reversed", "optc": "show high resistance with negative on anode and positive on cathode, and low resistance when reversed", "optd": "show low resistance in both directions", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What does a hall effect sensor sense?", "opta": "temperature", "optb": "moisture", "optc": "magnetic fields", "optd": "pressure", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What causes the piezoelectric effect?", "opta": "heat or dissimilar metals", "optb": "pressure on a crystal", "optc": "water running on iron", "optd": "a magnetic field", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which is the DIAC?", "opta": "", "optb": "", "optc": "", "optd": "", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A UJT has:", "opta": "two base leads", "optb": "one emitter lead", "optc": "two emitter leads and one base lead", "optd": "one emitter lead and two base leads", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The only way to close an SCR is with:", "opta": "a trigger input applied to the gate", "optb": "forward breakover voltage", "optc": "low-current dropout", "optd": "valley voltage", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is an SCR?", "opta": "a PNPN thyristor with 3 terminals", "optb": "a PNPN thyristor with 4 terminals", "optc": "a PNP thyristor with 3 terminals", "optd": "an NPN thyristor with 3 terminals", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What type of application would use a photovoltaic cell?", "opta": "an automobile horn", "optb": "a TI 92 calculator", "optc": "a magnetic field detector", "optd": "a remote power source", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which is the seven-segment display?", "opta": "", "optb": "", "optc": "", "optd": "", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The smallest amount of current that the cathode-anode can have, and still sustain conduction of an SCR is called the:", "opta": "maximum forward current", "optb": "maximum forward gate current", "optc": "holding current", "optd": "reverse gate leakage current", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Once a DIAC is conducting, the only way to turn it off is with:", "opta": "a positive gate voltage", "optb": "a negative gate voltage", "optc": "low-current dropout", "optd": "breakover", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which is the TRIAC?", "opta": "", "optb": "", "optc": "", "optd": "", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The DIAC is a:", "opta": "transistor", "optb": "unidirectional device", "optc": "three-layer device", "optd": "bidirectional device", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What type of application would use an injection laser diode?", "opta": "a 10BASE-T Ethernet", "optb": "a liquid crystal display", "optc": "a fiber optic transmission line", "optd": "a good flashlight", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The PUT (programmable unijunction transistor) is actually a type of:", "opta": "UJT thyristor", "optb": "FET device", "optc": "TRIAC", "optd": "SCR", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A transducer's function is to:", "opta": "transmit electrical energy", "optb": "convert energy", "optc": "produce mechanical energy", "optd": "prevent current flow", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}